The mind and body are hidden in the colon.
The word colon comes from koléon, the infinite.
I will talk a little about the cecum because it has a kind of digestive adaptation.
It's somewhat a place of revelation.
It's the verdict of your diet.
We will try to explore the tai chi of the colon, which we will link to the duodenal framework.
So remember that the main driver, ultimately, is this movement of the liver.
It’s this movement of air invited by the omentum.
It’s this motion.
of the establishment of the stomach. At the same time, you will have a whole
movement of
this yolk sac. The big fulcrum will be the dynamics of the brain with the heart,
to delve even deeper. In this phase of development, we see that it organizes
the digestive tract completely. It’s a rebalancing of
this dynamic between the brain,
the heart, and the return to this yolk sac.